

Lorna Bunnie contact@lornabunnie.co.uk

I have had artistic influence throughout my education due to years of experience with a variety of media, ranging from graphic design to fine art. After spending many years practising, I have developed a style which I think is unique and suitable for the concept and design of characters in animation. I am comfortable working in a team to produce work and can communicate effectively when issues arise. I have experience using software such as Photoshop and TV Paint, and with a passion for illustration I am working towards creating a steady skillset for 2D animation. I enjoy watching existing animation, utilising what I've learnt by applying it to my own work.

Software Experience

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Animate Adobe After Effects Adobe Premiere TV Paint

Work Experience

Assistant February 2011 - February 2011

Courtyard Arts

Freelance Work June 2017 - Present

Education and Qualifications

University of Hertfordshire **2015** - Present 2D Animation and Character for Digital Media BA (Hons) First and Second Year Overall Grades: 2:1 **Hertford Regional College** 2013 - 2015 **Art and Design BTEC Diploma** Merit Simon Balle School 9 GCSE's ranging from A - C (including Maths and English)

Interests and Activities

♥ I practice my skills by engaging in online communities drawing illustrations for popular cartoons.

2012 - 2013

- ♥ I take an interest in animal conservation, and own 3 rabbits.
- ♥ As well as illustration, I enjoy the art of fashion and try to incorporate this into my image.